# **Gregoriy Alexeev**

UI/UX Designer

Tbilisi, Georgia / +995 000-637-978 / greg.alexeev@me.com / Portfolio

A hard-working, motivated, and experienced **UI/UX Designer** with a strong online portfolio, attention to detail, and excellent management skills. Quick learner with modern ideas and a huge knowledge base. Having excellent communication skills I can easily fit a cross-functional **Agile team**. Always ready to perform tasks quickly in **different fields** like design, development, management, or analyses.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Senior UI/UX Designer Apr 2021 - Present Dualboot Partners, Charlotte, NC (Remote)

Designing complex user flows, researching personas, organizing design systems for **Web and Mobile** (iOS, Android) applications and SaaS. Communicating with product directors, stakeholders, and distributed developers team. Improving **design management** process and mentoring junior designers.

Senior UI/UX Designer Feb 2019 - Mar 2021

Coursly.co, Moscow

Designed an **online LMS** using the best practices of Interface Design in 6 months by implementing a system based on **reusable components**.

Increased the number of trial users by 400% with A/B testing.

Designed **onboarding** process and decreased a load of support center by 270%

Senior UI/UX Designer, Team Lead Sep 2016 - Feb 2019 #VA, Moscow

Managed a team of designers and developers. Worked with **customers'** requirements. Designed over 35 projects based on user interviews, prototypes and user flows. \$60,000 turnover of the company in its first year on the web design market. Built online courses with over 300 students who completed the course on UI/UX design.

Senior Web Developer Jun 2016 - May 2018

TechProMarketing, Boston, MA (Remote)

Full Stack Web Development. Landing Page and eCommerce websites design mockups integration. SEO optimization and API integration of Stripe and Plaid Processing. Built continuous integration (CI) for WordPress-based websites. Managed a team of 7 developers. Writing tech specs and documentation.

Junior UI Designer Jun 2014 - Dec 2014 AIC, Moscow

Web and mobile data-driven design (iOS & Android) of banking dashboards and financial services. Collaborating with the team to build a complex application design and usability testing. Designed system for the most popular Government Services Portal with 1,6M DAU.

## EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree - IT Management Sep 2015 - May 2019

Plekhanov Russian University of Economics, Moscow

Agile methodologies in IT Management and Web Technology.

### SKILLS

Expert in: UI/UX Design, Interaction Design, Adobe XD, Sketch, Web Design, Workflows, InvisionApp, Wireframes Design, Figma, Visual Design, Zoom, Slack, SaaS, Dashboards, Product Design, HTML5, CSS3

Intermediate in: Adobe Photoshop, WordPress, JavaScript, User Research,
Customer Journey Map, Design Team Management, Prototyping & User
Stories, Problem Solving skills, Other design tools, Laravel, Vue.js,
Video Editing, Onboarding design, Moqups, Zeplin, eCommerce Design

Basic In: Python, SQL, SEO, Motion Graphics, Graphic Design

### ONLINE PORTFOLIO

Check out my portfolio website with all the available projects, case studies, and other activities. Please note, that some of the marked projects are not for public sharing.